<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SantosTourGuide</string>
    <string name="vila_belmiro_title">Vila Belmiro</string>
    <string name="vila_belmiro_description">The stadium was inaugurated on October 12, 1916, however, its first match only took place 10 days later, with Santos winning against Ipiranga de São Paulo. In 1931 the lighting system was inaugurated, two years later the Stadium was renamed Urbano Caldeira. The club does monitored visitation and the tour includes the Memorial das Conquistas museum, changing rooms, the press room and the field, as well as the possibility of visiting the Training Center and the Recanto dos Alvinegros hotel through a previously scheduled visit."</string>
    <string name="historical_center_title">Historical Center</string>
    <string name="historical_center_description">It has several attractions that can be seen from a tourist tram that presents the historic center and crosses streets such as the 15th of November, where the coffee barons were concentrated in the middle of the 20th century, and shows an architectural sample of the richness of the time as in the Café Museum. In its surroundings, it had rich restaurants and cafeterias, currently average, but remains agitated by the commercial activity, services and the port.</string>
    <string name="shore_gardens_title">Shore Gardens</string>
    <string name="shore_gardens_description">The gardens on the Santos waterfront, located in Santos, a Brazilian city on the coast of São Paulo, form the largest beach front garden in extension in the world. The seafront extends through seven neighborhoods of the city: Aparecida, Boqueirão, Embaré, Gonzaga, José Menino, Pompeia and Ponta da Praia, and is a great source of biological resources and species of flowers and birds. The preservation and care for the flora of the Santos beach environment, permeated with palm and almond trees, are the result of a joint effort by the environmental departments of the region, often linked to universities or biological institutions.</string>
    <string name="plaza_text">Independence Plaza</string>
    <string name="plaza_description">Praça da Independência is a square in the city of Santos, in the state of São Paulo. It is known as the Heart of Gonzaga. Previously called Praça Municipal and Praça Marechal Deodoro. The name Praça da Independência was made official on February 16, 1921 and came into force in January 1922. In the Praça da Independência is the Monument to the Andradas, a tribute to the brothers José Bonifácio de Andrada e Silva, Martim Francisco Ribeiro de Andrada and Antônio Carlos Ribeiro de Andrada e Silva. Today, Praça da Independência is one of the main points of the city of Santos, concentrating popular manifestations and events, in addition to the great movement due to the commerce of that neighborhood.</string>
</resources>
